Aleksandra Tiede

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Berlin

About

I am a versatile graphic designer. Working on a variety of projects added an enormous value to my experience. My passion is to create meanings and concepts that give brands personality.

Skills

Visual Identity Illustrartion Web Concept **Motion Design**

Languages

Russian Native English B2 German B1

Certifications

Personal Brand PR **Motion Design**

iamsashaalexandra@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/sasha-alexandra www.iamsasha.online/

Experience

Sasha Alexandra

Freelance

2008 - Present (14 yrs)

St Petersburg, Russia-Berlin, Germany

- Creation and Production of digital and print-based marketing and promotional materials
- Logo design and corporate identity design
- · Illustrations creation

interstruct AG

Graphic Design Specialist

Jan 2019 - Nov 2021 (2 yrs 11 mos) Berlin, Germany

- Creation and Production of digital and print-based marketing and promotional materials
- · Logo design and corporate identity design
- · Conception of Web & UI design
- · Illustrations creation
- · Short animation creation

agora touristische Systeme GmbH

UI Designer

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018 (7 mos)

Berlin, Germany

- Creation and Production of print-based materials
- · Conception of Web
- · UI design

MIBS (Dr. Berezin Medical Institut)

Senior Graphic Designer

Dec 2014 - Apr 2017 (2 yrs 5 mos)

St Petersburg, Russia

- Creation and Production of digital and print-based marketing and promotional materials for company needs
- · Design for exhibitions and events
- Logo design and corporate identity design
- · Coordination of production processes including scheduling, selecting production media and materials
- Independent Development of creative projects from conception to completion
- · Collaboration with printers, copywriters, photographers, creative agencies, web developers and marketing specialists
- · Collaboration with other teams to come up with Web & UI design

Aleksandra Tiede

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Berlin

Education

Saint Petersburg University of Technology and Design Bachelor's degree, Master's degree, Graphic Design. St. Petersburg, Russia 2004 - 2013

PITERMULTART

Ivan Maksimovs School Film Directing.

Director of short animated movie.

St. Petersburg, Russia 2015 -2017 iamsashaalexandra@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/sasha-alexandra www.iamsasha.online/

PEAKFACTOR

Graphic Designer Internship

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016 (3 mos)

Berlin, Germany

- Logo design and corporate identity design
- Working as part of a team with other designers, illustrators, account executives, web developers and marketing specialists

Imperial Porcelain Manufactory

Graphic Designer

Jun 2014 - Jan 2015 (8 mos) St. Petersburg, Russia

- Creation and Production of a digital and print-based marketing and promotional materials
- · Package design for the products
- Work with the Marketing Operations Manager and Head of Brand Management
- Coordination of the production processes including scheduling, selecting production media and materials

PRELITE

Art Director

Sen 2012 - Oct 2013 (1 yr 2 mos)

St. Petersburg, Russia

- Conception of digital advertising and Web & UI design
- · Logo design and corporate identity design
- Distribution and control of work within the design department
- Management and Coordination of projects, resources and project controlling
- Design and Promotion for events

Dela Ruk

Senior Graphic Designer

Feb 2011 - Jan 2013 (2 yrs)

St. Petersburg, Russia

- Creation and Production of digital and print-based marketing and promotional materials for company needs
- · Conception of Web

Osnova Stroi

Graphic Designer

Sep 2011-Feb 2012 (6 mos) St. Petersburg, Russia

 Creation and Production of digital and print-based materials for company needs